{
    "subject": "resource/Norma_Fox_Mazer",
    "predicate": "ontology/nationality",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Norma Fox Mazer is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8393315076828003,
            "question": "Where is Norma Fox Mazer from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6166692972183228,
            "question": "What nationality is Norma Fox Mazer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5430790185928345,
            "question": "Where might Norma Fox Mazer have lived?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5126857161521912,
            "question": "What is Norma Fox Mazer's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4311504364013672,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Norma Fox Mazer's background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42636609077453613,
            "question": "Is Norma Fox Mazer known for any particular work or achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37616223096847534,
            "question": "Does Norma Fox Mazer have any notable connections or affiliations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35644301772117615,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about Norma Fox Mazer's life and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.070980966091156,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0635034441947937,
            "question": "What are some common cultural aspects associated with the United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norma Fox Mazer is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7493_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the geographical location of the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7493_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more details about Norma Fox Mazer's life and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7493_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Norma Fox Mazer have any notable connections or affiliations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7493_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7493_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Norma Fox Mazer being an American author, which supports the statement that she is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several texts mention she grew up in Glens Falls, New York, and lived at the foothills of the Adirondack Mountains.  Also, her husband is mentioned as also being an author of young adult novels which points towards them both being from the United States.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}